http://www.chandlerplacesenior.com/privacy-policy

Volunteer
Help protect our residents. We are closely monitoring the coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) situation.
Read More
Thank you for visiting this website and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Protecting your private information is a priority for us. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your information will be treated if it is collected through this website (the “Site”) by Chandler Place Limited Partnership, The Goodman Group, LLC, and their affiliates and related entities (collectively “Company,” “we”, “us” or “our”), and the choices that you (also “your”, “me”, “my” or “user”), as a visitor to this Site, can make about collection and use of your information. Except as explicitly provided herein, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to people that we do not employ or manage. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
Any dispute over privacy is subject to the Company’s Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. You should check this Site frequently to see recent changes in this Site’s Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use.
By accessing or using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Policy and the Site’s Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these terms, do not access or use the Site. This Policy addresses information collected through the Site. Additional or differing terms may apply to information otherwise collected by the Company.
1. What information is collected from me?
We collect two types of information about users of the Site: personally-identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personally-identifiable information (“NPII”). PII is information that identifies you personally and that you have voluntarily provided. NPII is information that does not identify you personally or is PII that has been scrubbed (i.e., deidentified). Unless otherwise provided, as used in this policy, the term “information” means all information collected about you on the Site, whether PII or NPII. PII is collected when you complete a form indicating interest in our services and/or requesting additional information (e.g. information about volunteering). The types of PII collected on these pages may include, but are not limited to, your name, email address, standard contact information including addresses and phone numbers. You also may provide additional PII to us when you conduct a search on this Site and participate in forums and chat rooms or other community features. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with PII regarding, for example, your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with the services we provide and contact preferences. Your participation in any of these activities (and therefore your provision of personally identifiable information) is entirely voluntary.
We may gather and collect NPII, including, but not limited to, any of the following: (1) IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous, (2) computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform, (3) the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from this Site, including date and time, (4) cookie number, and (5) Web pages and/or products you viewed or searched for. We may analyze this information for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of this Site users visit and how long they spend there. We may link NPII to PII to identify you. During some visits to the Site, we may use software tools such as Google Analytics to measure and collect session information (which is NPII), including page response times, download errors, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
We may gather and store certain types of NPII whenever you use this Site or the services made available on the Site (the “Services”). For example, like many websites, we may use “cookies,” and we may obtain certain types of NPII when your Web browser accesses this Site.
2. What are cookies and how are they used by the Company?
We may place Internet cookies on your Internet enabled device to help personalize your online experience. Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk by a web page server for record-keeping purposes. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or to deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are used to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service, (b) allow the Company to retrieve specific information from your registration on the Site or personalization of a page, for your convenience; (c) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Site to help target content based on user interests and behavior, and (d) measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Web pages of this Site may not display properly and/or you may not be permitted to access certain Site content and/or we may not be able to provide you with a personalized experience on this Site.
3. How is my information used?
The Company will not share or transfer your PII to others without your consent, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. In general, the information you provide will be used to support your consumer relationship with the Company. We want to help you quickly find content regarding the services on this Site and alert you to specific events, updated content and features, and other new products and services that are available. Notwithstanding the foregoing, the Company does research on our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of this Site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This aggregated information does not include PII. We may share this aggregated information with others. We also may combine your information with data we collect or receive from other companies and sources (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services.
4. Who is collecting my information?
Information is collected on the Site by or on behalf of the Company. If information is being collected and/or maintained by any entity other than the Company you will be notified, by means of a modification to this Privacy Policy, prior to the time of the information collection or transfer.
5. With whom does the Company share my information?
In addition to what is otherwise stated in this policy, the Company also may share information with the following groups: (a) affiliated businesses which the Company does not control but with which it engages in joint and co-branded offerings, (b) third party service providers in order to facilitate the performance of functions which are assigned to them, such as website operation and maintenance, order fulfillment, data analysis, marketing assistance, provision of search results and links, credit card payment processing, and customer service, and (c) entities with which Company may merge or which may acquire all or substantially all of Company’s assets, as such information likely will be one of the transferred assets. In addition, Company believes it is necessary to share information in order to: (i) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, and violations of standards of conduct, including the Terms of Use, (ii) respond to information requests by law enforcement agencies or government entities or if otherwise required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, court orders, or legal process, and (iii) establish or exercise our legal rights, or defend against legal claims, and as otherwise required by law. Company’s use of your information shall comply with applicable laws.
6. How do I access, update or delete my information?
To the extent that it can be identified as yours and is reasonably accessible, you can request the PII that Company has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your PII, request removal of PII from Company’s databases and/or update your PII by contacting webmaster@thegoodmangroup.com.
7. Do Not Track Notices and Settings
The Company does not monitor or address Do-Not-Track notices and settings by users.
8. What else should I know about my privacy?
Our Site may contain links to the websites of affiliated companies and to websites that are owned and operated by third parties. These other websites and services may have their own privacy policies and data collection practices independent of us. The Company has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post content that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information collected by Company; your providing of information to Company by use of the Site is at your own risk.
9. Children Under Thirteen.
The Site is not directed to nor intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any PII submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 13. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this Site.
10. Security
We take your privacy seriously and use tools such as encryption, passwords, and physical security to protect your information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no website can be absolutely secure, and third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from this Site. Therefore, although the Company works very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your information will always remain absolutely private.
11. Other legal notices
Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use, and will be governed and interpreted pursuant to the laws of Minnesota, United States of America, notwithstanding any principles of conflicts of law.
12. Contact us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about your privacy in connection with this policy or about the Company’s adherence to this policy, please send a thorough description to webmaster@thegoodmangroup.com.
13. Remarketing and Google Adwords
We use Google to provide remarketing services through Google Adwords. Google Adwords works by reading cookies placed on your computer. The cookies provide Google with information about you, such as searches you have made and products and services you have viewed on various websites. Google uses that information to show you targeted or personalized advertisements, in web search results and on other websites. This means you may receive targeted or personalized advertisements that result from your visit to the Site and information collected during of your visit.
You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies. The opt out process is described at:
https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
You can opt out of receiving some targeted or personalized advertisements as described by Google here:
https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en
You can learn about Google’s privacy practices by reviewing the Google Privacy Policy at:
https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
This version of the Privacy Policy is effective March 21, 2017.
